[{"Question":"Completethereplywiththepresentperfectsimpleorpresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbrackets.A:Haveyoufinishedthathistoryproject?B:No,Ihaven\u2019t.AndI_____________(do)itallday.","Answer":"\u2018vebeendoing","Id":"question-4161534-1"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:outofthis","Answer":"world","Id":"question-4161534-2"},{"Question":"Completethereplywiththepresentperfectsimpleorpresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbrackets.A.Didyouwritealettertothetowncouncil?B.Yes,butI__________(notsend)it.","Answer":"haven\u2019tsent","Id":"question-4161534-3"},{"Question":"Completethesentence.UsethePastsimpleorPresentperfectformoftheverbsinbrackets.\u2018Sorry,I\u2019mlate!__________(you/be)herelong?\u2019\u2018No,I____________(just/arrive).\u2019","Answer":"Haveyoubeen;havejustarrived","Id":"question-4161534-4"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:not_____________tostandard","Answer":"up","Id":"question-4161534-5"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:a_____________special","Answer":"bit","Id":"question-4161534-6"},{"Question":"\u0421hoosethetwocorrectoptionstomakeleisureactivities.Doyouwanttogo______thisweekend?","Answer":"skateboarding,iceskating","Id":"question-4161534-7"},{"Question":"Completethesentencewiththepresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbracketsandfororsince.I\u2019mgoinghome.I______(notfeel)well________thismorning.","Answer":"haven\u2019tbeenfeeling,since","Id":"question-4161534-8"},{"Question":"Completethereplywiththepresentperfectsimpleorpresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbrackets.A:Haveyoufinishedthathistoryproject?B:No,Ihaven\u2019t.AndI_____________(do)itallday.","Answer":"\u2018vebeendoing","Id":"question-4161534-1"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:outofthis","Answer":"world","Id":"question-4161534-2"},{"Question":"Completethereplywiththepresentperfectsimpleorpresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbrackets.A.Didyouwritealettertothetowncouncil?B.Yes,butI__________(notsend)it.","Answer":"haven\u2019tsent","Id":"question-4161534-3"},{"Question":"Completethesentence.UsethePastsimpleorPresentperfectformoftheverbsinbrackets.\u2018Sorry,I\u2019mlate!__________(you/be)herelong?\u2019\u2018No,I____________(just/arrive).\u2019","Answer":"Haveyoubeen;havejustarrived","Id":"question-4161534-4"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:not_____________tostandard","Answer":"up","Id":"question-4161534-5"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:a_____________special","Answer":"bit","Id":"question-4161534-6"},{"Question":"\u0421hoosethetwocorrectoptionstomakeleisureactivities.Doyouwanttogo______thisweekend?","Answer":"skateboarding,iceskating","Id":"question-4161534-7"},{"Question":"Completethesentencewiththepresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbracketsandfororsince.I\u2019mgoinghome.I______(notfeel)well________thismorning.","Answer":"haven\u2019tbeenfeeling,since","Id":"question-4161534-8"},{"Question":"Completethereplywiththepresentperfectsimpleorpresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbrackets.A:Haveyoufinishedthathistoryproject?B:No,Ihaven\u2019t.AndI_____________(do)itallday.","Answer":"\u2018vebeendoing","Id":"question-4161534-1"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:outofthis","Answer":"world","Id":"question-4161534-2"},{"Question":"Completethereplywiththepresentperfectsimpleorpresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbrackets.A.Didyouwritealettertothetowncouncil?B.Yes,butI__________(notsend)it.","Answer":"haven\u2019tsent","Id":"question-4161534-3"},{"Question":"Completethesentence.UsethePastsimpleorPresentperfectformoftheverbsinbrackets.\u2018Sorry,I\u2019mlate!__________(you/be)herelong?\u2019\u2018No,I____________(just/arrive).\u2019","Answer":"Haveyoubeen;havejustarrived","Id":"question-4161534-4"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:not_____________tostandard","Answer":"up","Id":"question-4161534-5"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:a_____________special","Answer":"bit","Id":"question-4161534-6"},{"Question":"\u0421hoosethetwocorrectoptionstomakeleisureactivities.Doyouwanttogo______thisweekend?","Answer":"skateboarding,iceskating","Id":"question-4161534-7"},{"Question":"Completethesentencewiththepresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbracketsandfororsince.I\u2019mgoinghome.I______(notfeel)well________thismorning.","Answer":"haven\u2019tbeenfeeling,since","Id":"question-4161534-8"},{"Question":"Completethereplywiththepresentperfectsimpleorpresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbrackets.A:Haveyoufinishedthathistoryproject?B:No,Ihaven\u2019t.AndI_____________(do)itallday.","Answer":"\u2018vebeendoing","Id":"question-4161534-1"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:outofthis","Answer":"world","Id":"question-4161534-2"},{"Question":"Completethereplywiththepresentperfectsimpleorpresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbrackets.A.Didyouwritealettertothetowncouncil?B.Yes,butI__________(notsend)it.","Answer":"haven\u2019tsent","Id":"question-4161534-3"},{"Question":"Completethesentence.UsethePastsimpleorPresentperfectformoftheverbsinbrackets.\u2018Sorry,I\u2019mlate!__________(you/be)herelong?\u2019\u2018No,I____________(just/arrive).\u2019","Answer":"Haveyoubeen;havejustarrived","Id":"question-4161534-4"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:not_____________tostandard","Answer":"up","Id":"question-4161534-5"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:a_____________special","Answer":"bit","Id":"question-4161534-6"},{"Question":"\u0421hoosethetwocorrectoptionstomakeleisureactivities.Doyouwanttogo______thisweekend?","Answer":"skateboarding,iceskating","Id":"question-4161534-7"},{"Question":"Completethesentencewiththepresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbracketsandfororsince.I\u2019mgoinghome.I______(notfeel)well________thismorning.","Answer":"haven\u2019tbeenfeeling,since","Id":"question-4161534-8"},{"Question":"Completethereplywiththepresentperfectsimpleorpresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbrackets.A:Haveyoufinishedthathistoryproject?B:No,Ihaven\u2019t.AndI_____________(do)itallday.","Answer":"\u2018vebeendoing","Id":"question-4161534-1"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:outofthis","Answer":"world","Id":"question-4161534-2"},{"Question":"Completethereplywiththepresentperfectsimpleorpresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbrackets.A.Didyouwritealettertothetowncouncil?B.Yes,butI__________(notsend)it.","Answer":"haven\u2019tsent","Id":"question-4161534-3"},{"Question":"Completethesentence.UsethePastsimpleorPresentperfectformoftheverbsinbrackets.\u2018Sorry,I\u2019mlate!__________(you/be)herelong?\u2019\u2018No,I____________(just/arrive).\u2019","Answer":"Haveyoubeen;havejustarrived","Id":"question-4161534-4"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:not_____________tostandard","Answer":"up","Id":"question-4161534-5"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:a_____________special","Answer":"bit","Id":"question-4161534-6"},{"Question":"\u0421hoosethetwocorrectoptionstomakeleisureactivities.Doyouwanttogo______thisweekend?","Answer":"skateboarding,iceskating","Id":"question-4161534-7"},{"Question":"Completethesentencewiththepresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbracketsandfororsince.I\u2019mgoinghome.I______(notfeel)well________thismorning.","Answer":"haven\u2019tbeenfeeling,since","Id":"question-4161534-8"},{"Question":"\u0421\u043F\u0440\u043E\u0441\u0442\u0456\u0442\u044C\u0432\u0438\u0440\u0430\u0437(\u0437\u043C\u0456\u043D\u043D\u0456\u043D\u0430\u0431\u0443\u0432\u0430\u044E\u0442\u044C\u043D\u0435\u0432\u0456\u0434\u2019\u0454\u043C\u043D\u0438\u0445\u0437\u043D\u0430\u0447\u0435\u043D\u044C)","Answer":null,"Id":"question-4208966-1"},{"Question":"\u0413\u0440\u0430\u0444\u0456\u043A\u044F\u043A\u043E\u0457\u0444\u0443\u043D\u043A\u0446\u0456\u0457\u0437\u043E\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0436\u0435\u043D\u043E\u043D\u0430\u0440\u0438\u0441\u0443\u043D\u043A\u0443?","Answer":null,"Id":"question-4208966-2"},{"Question":null,"Answer":null,"Id":"question-4208966-3"},{"Question":"\u0412\u043A\u0430\u0436\u0456\u0442\u044C\u043E\u0431\u043B\u0430\u0441\u0442\u044C\u0432\u0438\u0437\u043D\u0430\u0447\u0435\u043D\u043D\u044F\u0444\u0443\u043D\u043A\u0446\u0456\u0457","Answer":"R","Id":"question-4208966-4"},{"Question":"\u0420\u043E\u0437\u0432\u0027\u044F\u0437\u0430\u0442\u0438\u0440\u0456\u0432\u043D\u044F\u043D\u043D\u044F:\u0445","Answer":"2","Id":"question-4208966-5"},{"Question":"\u0421\u0430\u043C\u043A\u0430\u0448\u0438\u043C\u043F\u0430\u043D\u0437\u0435\u043C\u0430\u0454\u0406\u0433\u0440\u0443\u043F\u0443\u043A\u0440\u043E\u0432\u0456\u0437\u0430\u0441\u0438\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043C\u043E\u044E\u0410\u04120\u0442\u0430\u043D\u043E\u0440\u043C\u0430\u043B\u044C\u043D\u0443\u043F\u0456\u0433\u043C\u0435\u043D\u0442\u0430\u0446\u0456\u044E,\u0430\u0443\u0441\u0430\u043C\u0446\u044FIV\u0433\u0440\u0443\u043F\u0430\u043A\u0440\u043E\u0432\u0456\u0439\u0430\u043B\u044C\u0431\u0456\u043D\u0456\u0437\u043C.\u042F\u043A\u0430\u0432\u0456\u0440\u043E\u0433\u0456\u0434\u043D\u0456\u0441\u0442\u044C\u043D\u0430\u0440\u043E\u0434\u0436\u0435\u043D\u043D\u044F\u043D\u0430\u0449\u0430\u0434\u043A\u0456\u0432\u0437\u0406\u0406\u0406\u0433\u0440\u0443\u043F\u043E\u044E\u043A\u0440\u043E\u0432\u0456\u0439\u043D\u043E\u0440\u043C\u0430\u043B\u044C\u043D\u043E\u044E\u043F\u0456\u0433\u043C\u0435\u043D\u0442\u0430\u0446\u0456\u0454\u044E(\u0441\u0430\u043C\u043A\u0430\u0433\u043E\u043C\u043E\u0437\u0438\u0433\u043E\u0442\u043D\u0430\u0437\u0430\u043E\u0437\u043D\u0430\u043A\u043E\u044E\u043F\u0456\u0433\u043C\u0435\u043D\u0442\u0430\u0446\u0456\u0457)?","Answer":"50%","Id":"question-4562565-1"},{"Question":"\u0421\u0430\u043C\u043A\u0430\u0448\u0438\u043C\u043F\u0430\u043D\u0437\u0435\u043C\u0430\u0454\u0406\u0433\u0440\u0443\u043F\u0443\u043A\u0440\u043E\u0432\u0456\u0437\u0430\u0441\u0438\u0441\u0442\u0435\u043C\u043E\u044E\u0410\u04120\u0442\u0430\u043D\u043E\u0440\u043C\u0430\u043B\u044C\u043D\u0443\u043F\u0456\u0433\u043C\u0435\u043D\u0442\u0430\u0446\u0456\u044E,\u0430\u0443\u0441\u0430\u043C\u0446\u044FIV\u0433\u0440\u0443\u043F\u0430\u043A\u0440\u043E\u0432\u0456\u0439\u0430\u043B\u044C\u0431\u0456\u043D\u0456\u0437\u043C.\u042F\u043A\u0430\u0432\u0456\u0440\u043E\u0433\u0456\u0434\u043D\u0456\u0441\u0442\u044C\u043D\u0430\u0440\u043E\u0434\u0436\u0435\u043D\u043D\u044F\u043D\u0430\u0449\u0430\u0434\u043A\u0456\u0432\u0437\u0406\u0406\u0433\u0440\u0443\u043F\u043E\u044E\u043A\u0440\u043E\u0432\u0456\u0439\u0430\u043B\u044C\u0431\u0456\u043D\u0456\u0437\u043C\u043E\u043C(\u0441\u0430\u043C\u043A\u0430\u0433\u0435\u0442\u0435\u0440\u043E\u0437\u0438\u0433\u043E\u0442\u043D\u0430\u0437\u0430\u043E\u0437\u043D\u0430\u043A\u043E\u044E\u043F\u0456\u0433\u043C\u0435\u043D\u0442\u0430\u0446\u0456\u0457)?","Answer":"25%","Id":"question-4562565-2"},{"Question":"\u0423\u043B\u044E\u0434\u0438\u043D\u0438\u0433\u0435\u043D\u043A\u0430\u0440\u043E\u043E\u043A\u043E\u0441\u0442\u0456\u0434\u043E\u043C\u0456\u043D\u0443\u0454\u043D\u0430\u0434\u0433\u0435\u043D\u043E\u043C\u0431\u043B\u0430\u043A\u0438\u0442\u043D\u043E\u043E\u043A\u043E\u0441\u0442\u0456,\u0430\u0432\u043C\u0456\u043D\u043D\u044F\u0432\u043E\u043B\u043E\u0434\u0456\u0442\u0438\u043F\u0440\u0430\u0432\u043E\u044E\u0440\u0443\u043A\u043E\u044E\u2013\u043D\u0430\u0434\u043B\u0456\u0432\u043E\u0440\u0443\u043A\u0456\u0441\u0442\u044E.\u0426\u0456\u043F\u0430\u0440\u0438\u0433\u0435\u043D\u0456\u0432\u0440\u043E\u0437\u043C\u0456\u0449\u0435\u043D\u0456\u0432\u0440\u0456\u0437\u043D\u0438\u0445\u0445\u0440\u043E\u043C\u043E\u0441\u043E\u043C\u0430\u0445.\u042F\u043A\u0438\u043C\u0438\u0431\u0443\u0434\u0443\u0442\u044C\u0434\u0456\u0442\u0438,\u044F\u043A\u0449\u043E\u043C\u0430\u0442\u0438\u0431\u043B\u0430\u043A\u0438\u0442\u043D\u043E\u043E\u043A\u0430\u0439\u0433\u0435\u0442\u0435\u0440\u043E\u0437\u0438\u0433\u043E\u0442\u043D\u0430\u0437\u0430\u043F\u0440\u0430\u0432\u043E\u0440\u0443\u043A\u0456\u0441\u0442\u044E,\u0430\u0431\u0430\u0442\u044C\u043A\u043E\u2013\u043B\u0456\u0432\u0448\u0430\u0439\u0433\u0435\u0442\u0435\u0440\u043E\u0437\u0438\u0433\u043E\u0442\u043D\u0438\u0439\u0437\u0430\u043A\u043E\u043B\u044C\u043E\u0440\u043E\u043C\u043E\u0447\u0435\u0439?","Answer":"25%\u043A\u0430\u0440\u043E\u043E\u043A\u0456\u043F\u0440\u0430\u0432\u043E\u0440\u0443\u043A\u0456;25%\u043A\u0430\u0440\u043E\u043E\u043A\u0456\u043B\u0456\u0432\u043E\u0440\u0443\u043A\u0456;25%\u0431\u043B\u0430\u043A\u0438\u0442\u043D\u043E\u043E\u043A\u0456\u043B\u0456\u0432\u043E\u0440\u0443\u043A\u0456;25%\u0431\u043B\u0430\u043A\u0438\u0442\u043D\u043E\u043E\u043A\u0456\u043F\u0440\u0430\u0432\u043E\u0440\u0443\u043A\u0456;","Id":"question-4562565-3"},{"Question":"\u042F\u043A\u0438\u0439\u0437\u043A\u043E\u0442\u0456\u0432\u0454\u0434\u0438\u0433\u0435\u0442\u0435\u0440\u043E\u0437\u0438\u0433\u043E\u0442\u043D\u0438\u043C?","Answer":"\u0437\u0433\u0435\u043D\u043E\u0442\u0438\u043F\u043E\u043CSsBb","Id":"question-4562565-4"},{"Question":null,"Answer":"\u0430\u0430bb","Id":"question-4562565-5"},{"Question":null,"Answer":"\u0430\u0430\u0406\u0410\u0406\u0412","Id":"question-4562565-6"},{"Question":"Completethereplywiththepresentperfectsimpleorpresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbrackets.A:Haveyoufinishedthathistoryproject?B:No,Ihaven\u2019t.AndI_____________(do)itallday.","Answer":"\u2018vebeendoing","Id":"question-4161534-1"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:outofthis","Answer":"world","Id":"question-4161534-2"},{"Question":"Completethereplywiththepresentperfectsimpleorpresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbrackets.A.Didyouwritealettertothetowncouncil?B.Yes,butI__________(notsend)it.","Answer":"haven\u2019tsent","Id":"question-4161534-3"},{"Question":"Completethesentence.UsethePastsimpleorPresentperfectformoftheverbsinbrackets.\u2018Sorry,I\u2019mlate!__________(you/be)herelong?\u2019\u2018No,I____________(just/arrive).\u2019","Answer":"Haveyoubeen;havejustarrived","Id":"question-4161534-4"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:not_____________tostandard","Answer":"up","Id":"question-4161534-5"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:a_____________special","Answer":"bit","Id":"question-4161534-6"},{"Question":"\u0421hoosethetwocorrectoptionstomakeleisureactivities.Doyouwanttogo______thisweekend?","Answer":"skateboarding,iceskating","Id":"question-4161534-7"},{"Question":"Completethesentencewiththepresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbracketsandfororsince.I\u2019mgoinghome.I______(notfeel)well________thismorning.","Answer":"haven\u2019tbeenfeeling,since","Id":"question-4161534-8"},{"Question":"Completethereplywiththepresentperfectsimpleorpresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbrackets.A:Haveyoufinishedthathistoryproject?B:No,Ihaven\u2019t.AndI_____________(do)itallday.","Answer":"\u2018vebeendoing","Id":"question-4161534-1"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:outofthis","Answer":"world","Id":"question-4161534-2"},{"Question":"Completethereplywiththepresentperfectsimpleorpresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbrackets.A.Didyouwritealettertothetowncouncil?B.Yes,butI__________(notsend)it.","Answer":"haven\u2019tsent","Id":"question-4161534-3"},{"Question":"Completethesentence.UsethePastsimpleorPresentperfectformoftheverbsinbrackets.\u2018Sorry,I\u2019mlate!__________(you/be)herelong?\u2019\u2018No,I____________(just/arrive).\u2019","Answer":"Haveyoubeen;havejustarrived","Id":"question-4161534-4"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:not_____________tostandard","Answer":"up","Id":"question-4161534-5"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:a_____________special","Answer":"bit","Id":"question-4161534-6"},{"Question":"\u0421hoosethetwocorrectoptionstomakeleisureactivities.Doyouwanttogo______thisweekend?","Answer":"skateboarding,iceskating","Id":"question-4161534-7"},{"Question":"Completethesentencewiththepresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbracketsandfororsince.I\u2019mgoinghome.I______(notfeel)well________thismorning.","Answer":"haven\u2019tbeenfeeling,since","Id":"question-4161534-8"},{"Question":"Completethereplywiththepresentperfectsimpleorpresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbrackets.A:Haveyoufinishedthathistoryproject?B:No,Ihaven\u2019t.AndI_____________(do)itallday.","Answer":"\u2018vebeendoing","Id":"question-4161534-1"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:outofthis","Answer":"world","Id":"question-4161534-2"},{"Question":"Completethereplywiththepresentperfectsimpleorpresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbrackets.A.Didyouwritealettertothetowncouncil?B.Yes,butI__________(notsend)it.","Answer":"haven\u2019tsent","Id":"question-4161534-3"},{"Question":"Completethesentence.UsethePastsimpleorPresentperfectformoftheverbsinbrackets.\u2018Sorry,I\u2019mlate!__________(you/be)herelong?\u2019\u2018No,I____________(just/arrive).\u2019","Answer":"Haveyoubeen;havejustarrived","Id":"question-4161534-4"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:not_____________tostandard","Answer":"up","Id":"question-4161534-5"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:a_____________special","Answer":"bit","Id":"question-4161534-6"},{"Question":"\u0421hoosethetwocorrectoptionstomakeleisureactivities.Doyouwanttogo______thisweekend?","Answer":"skateboarding,iceskating","Id":"question-4161534-7"},{"Question":"Completethesentencewiththepresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbracketsandfororsince.I\u2019mgoinghome.I______(notfeel)well________thismorning.","Answer":"haven\u2019tbeenfeeling,since","Id":"question-4161534-8"},{"Question":"Completethereplywiththepresentperfectsimpleorpresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbrackets.A:Haveyoufinishedthathistoryproject?B:No,Ihaven\u2019t.AndI_____________(do)itallday.","Answer":"\u2018vebeendoing","Id":"question-4161534-1"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:outofthis","Answer":"world","Id":"question-4161534-2"},{"Question":"Completethereplywiththepresentperfectsimpleorpresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbrackets.A.Didyouwritealettertothetowncouncil?B.Yes,butI__________(notsend)it.","Answer":"haven\u2019tsent","Id":"question-4161534-3"},{"Question":"Completethesentence.UsethePastsimpleorPresentperfectformoftheverbsinbrackets.\u2018Sorry,I\u2019mlate!__________(you/be)herelong?\u2019\u2018No,I____________(just/arrive).\u2019","Answer":"Haveyoubeen;havejustarrived","Id":"question-4161534-4"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:not_____________tostandard","Answer":"up","Id":"question-4161534-5"},{"Question":"Completetheusefulphrasewiththeappropriateword:a_____________special","Answer":"bit","Id":"question-4161534-6"},{"Question":"\u0421hoosethetwocorrectoptionstomakeleisureactivities.Doyouwanttogo______thisweekend?","Answer":"skateboarding,iceskating","Id":"question-4161534-7"},{"Question":"Completethesentencewiththepresentperfectcontinuousformoftheverbinbracketsandfororsince.I\u2019mgoinghome.I______(notfeel)well________thismorning.","Answer":"haven\u2019tbeenfeeling,since","Id":"question-4161534-8"}]